本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： HTC 华青墨 Simile176 小坏玩意儿
校对： 唱唱反调  后期： 唱唱反调
西蒙
Simon.
只有我 哈瑞
It's just me, Harry.
别紧张伙计
Don't freak out man.
西蒙
Simon?
嗨 伙计 你没事吧
Hey, man, are you OK?
救命 救命
Help! Help!
救救救救救命
HEEEEEELP!
# 我今早起床 #
I got out of bed today
# 对上帝发誓我看不见我的脸 #
Swear to god I couldn't see my face
# 我今早起床注视着一缕灵魂 #
I got out of bed today staring at a ghost
# 你看到我的灵魂了么 #
Oh have you seen my ghost
# 感觉到它了么 看到它了么 #
Seen my ghost, seen my ghost?
# 你看到我的灵魂了么 它凝视着地面 #
Oh, have you seen my ghost staring at the ground?
心灵缉凶 第二季第3集
行动起来
Let's move.
昨晚某个时辰有个流浪汉被杀了
We've got a homeless man killed sometime last night.
现场警察称之为"迷上疯狂"
Uniforms on scene called it in as "Crazy on Crazy".
什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
应该给他们来些敏感性训练
They're due for some sensitivity training.
但很明显这是起心理犯罪
But this is definitely one for Psych Crimes.
- 情节非常匪夷所思 - 比如说
- Very bizarre details. - Such as?
你会发现的
You'll see.
- 凶案组在查这个案子吗 - 要联合调查
- Homicide on this one? - It's a joint investigation,
不过大清早
but there was a gang shooting
在狄斯路上发生了持枪火拼案
on Dixie Road early this morning,
多个凶杀案 所以这个现在是你的了
multiple homicides, so this one's yours for now,
但他们赶上来时要让他们知情
but keep them in the loop when they catch up with you.
那就是发现尸体的人
That's who found the body.
我认识他
I know him.
- 他是疑犯吗 - 哈瑞 我表示怀疑
- Is he a suspect? - Harry? I doubt it.
他可是相当人畜无害
He's pretty harmless.
好好看着他 让里奥引导 但是...
Take a good look at him. I mean, let Leo lead, but...
明白 他已经取得联系了
I know. He's got the touch.
嘿 哈瑞
Hey, Harry.
你还好吗 我的朋友
How are you doing, my friend?
是我 里奥
It's me. Leo.
- 里奥 - 去年我经常去看你
- Leo? - I used to see you last year,
那是你正被汉伯困扰
when you were hanging over by the Humber.
你现在住在这里吗
You living down here now?
我只是拜访 我是个护士 记得吗
I'm just visiting. I'm a nurse, remember?
这是我朋友波比 她是个警察
This is my friend Poppy. She's a police officer.
我不喜欢条子
I don't like cops.
漂白剂(的味道吗)
Bleach?
对 整个现场都被冲刷了
Yeah, the whole scene's been washed down.
没有武器的迹象
There's no sign of the weapon,
并且尸体是在人死后摆成这样的
and the body's been staged post-mortem.
这个现场很复杂
It's a complicated scene.
他的喉咙被切断了吗
His throat was cut?
对 颈静脉和颈动脉都被割断了
Yeah, both the jugular vein and the carotid artery were
克莉格拉 先别跟媒体说
severed. Caligra. Let's keep that out of the media.
血都哪里去了呢
Where's all the blood?
这些可能是自卫受得伤
These could be defensive wounds.
他挣扎了 所以刀划到了一些其他地方
He struggled, knife bounced around a bit.
但接下来的这个
But then there's this.
- 更多自卫伤口吗 - 伤口太浅了
- More defensive wounds? - Too superficial.
手和胳膊在持刀搏斗中自卫受得伤
Defensive wounds on hands and arms in a knife fight
通常都会切至骨头的
usually cut to the bone.
这些伤至少有些时日了 我说得对吗
These are at least a few days old, am I right?
正确
Yeah.
这些伤痕看起来也像旧的
These injuries look older as well.
这孩子过去几周
This kid has taken some serious beatings
遭受过严重毒打
in the last few weeks.
貌似这些伤都是他磨出来的
Looks like he's been dishing 'em out too.
你能描述一下
Can you describe
你发现时尸体的样子吗
what the body looked like when you found it?
我不想谈论此事
I don't want to talk about it.
对不起 哈瑞 但你必须得说
I'm sorry, Harry, but you're gonna have to.
如果你不肯配合警方
If you don't cooperate with the police,
他们会开始对原因有疑惑
they're gonna start wondering why.
好了
OK.
好吧
我只是去看西蒙
I was just... going to see Simon
给他带回了些菜
and bring him back his dish.
- 被害人叫西蒙 - 是的
- The victim's name was Simon? - Yeah.
你知道他姓什么吗
Do you know his last name?
卡林 科里
Carling? Curley?
凯利
Kelly.
我觉得是凯利
I think it was Kelly.
这么说 西蒙是你的朋友喽
So, Simon was your friend?
西蒙是我的朋友
Simon was my friend.
- 我们都有些什么线索 - 你知道什么
- So, what have we got? - What do you know?
流浪汉 被割喉
Homeless guy. Throat cut.
有关于现场被抹干净的吗
Something about the whole scene being wiped clean?
漂白剂 大量漂白剂
With bleach. A lot of it.
有人大费周章地区消灭证据
Someone went to a lot of trouble to destroy evidence.
我们认为远不止这样
Well, we think there's more to it than that.
瞧这尸体造型摆得多仔细啊
Look how carefully the body is posed...
干净的衬衫 纽扣紧扣 好像是为隐藏切口
clean shirt, all buttoned-up, as if to hide the cut.
整个现场都有某种痴迷的感觉
There is something obsessive about the whole scene.
痴迷于逃脱被捕
Obsessed with not getting caught.
以及或者说是痴迷于消除暴力迹象
And/or obsessed with erasing signs of violence.
为什么洗墙呢
Why wash the walls?
我们又不会漏掉他被割喉
It's not like we're gonna miss the guy's throat was cut.
好吧 我知道为什么这是起心理犯罪了
OK. I see why it's a psych crime.
你很幸运
Lucky for you.
怎么会
How so?
这意味着调查警司布莱克
It means Detective Sergeant Black
可以承担高水平职责
can assume the high-level responsibilities
参与这样一个异常敏感的案子
involved in a uniquely sensitive case like this.
那意味着在她返回调查狄斯路杀人案时
It means I get to do the grunt work on a homeless
我得处理枯燥乏味繁重的谋杀流浪汉案
murder while she gets back to the killings on Dixie Road.
差不多是这样 你能替我担负这个责任吗
Pretty much. You can carry the ball for me on this?
有情况会及时通知你的
I'll keep you in the loop.
谢谢你 艾登
Thank you, Aidan.
你跟这个警探 有过一段历史吗
You and the detective - some history there?
理耶特 历史 对 没什么大不了的
Liette? History? Yeah. As in not an issue.
- 很显然 - 有什么好消息吗
- Obviously. - Any luck?
我想我们确认了死者的身份
Think we've got an ID for our victim.
发现尸体的流浪汉告诉我们一个名字
Homeless guy who found the body gave us a name.
西蒙凯利
Simon Kelly.
- 就是他 - 二十二岁
- That's him. - Age 22.
十六岁时被诊断为患有精神分裂症
Diagnosed with schizophrenia when he was 16.
从那时至今经常进进出出医院
In and out of hospitals ever since.
有他的档案吗
He got a record?
没有 被警察逮到过几次
No. Picked up by uniforms a couple times,
不过都直接被送去精神病病房
but taken straight to the psych ward.
当然 那不应该收录在档的
Yeah, that shouldn't be in his record.
有精神分裂又不是犯罪
Having schizophrenia is not a crime.
就我而言 我想知道
Personally, I'd like to know.
发现他的那个人呢
How about the guy who found him?
哈瑞布拉克斯顿 可以排除他的嫌疑了
Harry Braxton. We can rule him out as a suspect.
他的手和衣服都很干净 无血迹 总之
His hands and clothes are clean - of blood, anyway...
他看着不像过不久洗干净的
and... it doesn't look like he's washed in a while.
他对西蒙凯利了解多少
How well did he know Simon Kelly?
他说他们曾是最好的朋友 可爱的小伙子
He says they were best friends - lovely guy,
没有敌人 任何人都没有理由想要伤害他
no enemies, no reason anyone would want to hurt him.
有暴力史吗
Any history of violence?
哈瑞说他连苍蝇都不会伤害
Harry says he wouldn't hurt a fly.
这跟他身体上的痕迹可不相符啊
That doesn't fit with the marks on his body.
有什么近亲吗
Any next of kin?
他的父母 罗伯特凯利和爱丽丝凯利夫妇
His parents, Robert and Alice Kelly.
你们继续仔细搜查山谷
You guys keep canvassing the valley.
看能否找到知道些什么的人
See if you can find anyone who knows anything.
你要一起去吗
You want to come with?
你以前做过死亡通报吗
You ever done a death notification before?
在医院做过
At the hospital.
这会有些许不同
Well, this is a little bit different.
我们突然出现
We're showing up out of the blue
并且带来的消息可能是最坏的
with the worst news possible.
所以表现出同情和支持是很要紧的
And it's important to be sympathetic and supportive.
明白了
Got it.
不 这是谋杀调查
No. This is a murder investigation;
在被证实之前每个人都有嫌疑
everyone's a suspect until they're not.
我们的任务是获取尽可能多地信息
Our job is to get as much information as possible
不放过任何蛛丝马迹
without giving anything away.
确实不一样
Wow. That is different.
有点像同情和支持的对立面
It's kind of the opposite of sympathetic and supportive.
- 还有什么是我得知道的吗 - 有
- Anything else I should know? - Yeah.
我宁可挨枪子也不愿这么做
I'd rather take a bullet than do this.
准备好了吗
You ready?
- 罗伯特凯利 - 什么事
- Robert Kelly? - Yes?
我是艾登 布莱克警探
My name is Detective Aidan Black.
麦德龙警局的 这位是克拉拉马龙医生
I'm with the Metro Police. This is Dr. Clara Malone...
西蒙 西蒙出事了
Simon. Something's happened to Simon.
他不是个坏人
He wasn't a bad person.
你们得理解 他病得非常 非常重
You have to understand, he was very, very sick.
我们理解 凯利夫人
We understand, Mrs. Kelly.
那他是怎么死的
So, how did he die?
我们要等尸检报告出来
We're waiting for the autopsy
才能做出推断
report before making a determination.
你们上次见到西蒙是什么时候
When was the last time you saw Simon?
- 很久以前 我们很久没见过他了 - 对
- Never. We never saw him. - Yeah,
我们和西蒙已经有几年没联系了
we haven't had contact with Simon in a couple of years.
我们也别无选择
Not our choice.
是他不愿意见你们吗
So he refused to see you?
能告诉我们原因吗
Can I ask why?
他有精神分裂症 警探先生
He had schizophrenia, Detective.
谁知道他怎么想的
Who knows why he did anything?
他不愿让我们帮他
He didn't want us to help him.
他不知道我们这是为了他好
He didn't understand it was for his own good.
他... 他会变得很愤怒
He'd... he would get so angry...
- 我们应该更尽力一些的 - 爱丽丝
- We should've fought harder. - Alice.
行了 让我说吧
Please, just... would you let me do this?
这事让我们备受煎熬
This has been extremely difficult for us.
尤其是我的妻子
Uh... especially for my wife.
爱丽丝在他刚得病那段时间全天候的照顾他
Alice cared for Simon full time when he first became ill.
到头来却发现
And then eventually we found out that
他流落街头
he was living on the street.
他有自己的法律代表
He had a case worker,
但她什么事都没告诉我们
but she wouldn't tell us anything.
她说这是为了保护他的隐私
She said it was to protect his privacy.
可现在呢 有谁能保护他呢
Well, who's protecting him now?
到底发生了什么
What happened?
是毒品 还是... 疾病
Drugs? Or... some sort of disease?
他是被谋杀的 爸爸
He was murdered, Dad.
懂了吗 不然你以为他们来干什么
OK? Why do you think they're still here?
是真的吗
Is that true?
具体情况还在调查中 先生
The investigation is ongoing, sir.
失陪一下
If I may...
我能和你坐一会儿吗
Mind if I join you?
西蒙被诊断出有病的时候你多大 十二岁吗
You were, what, 12 when Simon was diagnosed?
我有很多患精神分裂症的病人
I've had a number of patients with schizophrenia.
我知道这对家庭来说很艰难
I know how hard it is on the family.
病人 我以为你也是警察
Patients? I thought you were a cop.
精神科医生
Forensic psychiatrist.
你是想了解西蒙
Ah, you want to know about Simon. Um...
典型的症状 你知道的 幻听 不洗澡
Textbook case. You know, heard voices, stopped showering,
会对着灯柱大吼大叫 都是常见病症
yelled at lamp posts. You know, "The ush".
曼迪 我不是来帮助西蒙的
Maddie, I'm not here to help Simon.
他已经去世了
He's dead.
那你来干什么
Then why are you here?
如果我们能弄清楚你哥哥的死因 也许
If we can figure out what happened to your brother, maybe
你和你的家人能因此得到慰藉
you and your family can get some closure.
你不希望这样吗
You don't want that?
我见过这样的情况
I've seen what happens
当亲生兄妹得了精神分裂症
when a sibling develops schizophrenia.
他们病得越重 得到的照顾就越多
The worse they act, the more attention they get.
不用多久
Pretty soon
家里其他的孩子就会被忽视
the other kids in the family are getting nothing.
无论他们多优秀
No matter how good they are,
无论他们等了多久
no matter how long they wait for their turn,
都得不到父母的关注
it never comes.
你是这么觉得吗
Is that how you felt?
你是说我是否
You mean, am I so starved for attention
非常渴求父母的关注吗
to fall for your little act?
不是我不懂礼貌 但我们家
I don't want to be rude, but we've been
不依赖外人照顾过西蒙好几年了
dealing with Simon on our own for years, so, you know,
所以我觉得讽刺的是你们来到我家
I think it's kind of ironic, you coming here,
拒绝透露他的死因
refusing to say how he died, and then, what,
却想要了解我们的生活
expecting me to spill my whole life story?
我不需要你的帮助 懂吗
I don't need your help, OK?
我过得很好
My life is fine.
西蒙经常惹麻烦吗
Did Simon get into a lot of fights?
没有 他从来不会伤害任何人 是谁告诉你的
No. He would never hurt anyone. Who told you that?
这不是真的 告诉他们这不是真的
It's not true. Tell them it's not true.
你们知道有谁会想伤害西蒙吗
Do you know anyone who wanted to hurt Simon?
抱歉 打断一下
Excuse me,
你是想说他是被谋杀的吗
are you saying that he was murdered?
很抱歉 先生 我...
I'm sorry, sir, I...
我们应该强迫他待在家里的
We should have forced him to stay at home.
他为什么不让我照顾他
Why wouldn't he let me take care of him?
别这么说 别这么说
Please, please.
行了
OK...
给我们点时间吧 抱歉
you're going to have to give us some time. I'm sorry.
能否请你们
Why don't you come back
准备好告诉我们儿子的死因时再来
when you're prepared to tell us what happened to our son?
节哀
I'm sorry for your loss.
我们会联系你的
We'll be in touch.
这算是常见的情况吗
Is that what it's usually like?
从来没什么常见的情况 你有什么收获吗
There's no usual. What's your take?
他们的女儿什么都不肯透露
The daughter is completely shut down.
母亲质疑自己过去所做的一切
Mom is second-guessing everything she ever did.
父亲发怒
And the father is in a rage
因为觉得自己无力帮助家人
because he feels powerless to fix the family.
可能因为他们很久没见过西蒙
Probably made worse by the fact that they haven't
- 感觉会越发糟糕 - 他们会不知所措
- seen Simon in so long. - They're reeling.
当西蒙这样的人死后
When someone like Simon dies,
家人会感到如释重负
the family often feels relief
却又悲痛不已 感情非常复杂
as well as grief. It's confusing,
他们会有愧疚感 木已成舟无法挽回
they feel guilty, and it's downhill from there.
现在说什么都太晚了
And now it's too late.
对西蒙来说是晚了
Well, too late for Simon.
但对他的家庭来说并不晚
But there's still a family there.
你好 有人在吗
Hey there. Anybody home?
这个月底
You know the city is gonna do its annual sweep
市里会开展年度大清扫
at the end of this month,
把所有一起的帐篷和棚户全部清理掉
clear out all the tents and shelters.
希望那些地方在那之前能保住
May as well keep it dry until then.
你可真是心软
You are such a bleeding heart.
是啊 没错
Yeah, sure, sure.
他死了
He's dead.
两个流浪汉 同一处山谷
Two homeless men, same ravine,
相隔仅数日
within a few days of each other.
你真觉得这是巧合吗
You really think that's a coincidence?
他们都受了外伤 街头流浪的日子不好过
So they both had bruises. Life on the street is rough.
我也说不清
I don't know.
像是他们突然想要打架 然后就死了
It's like they suddenly took up kickboxing, then died.
犯罪现场的情况完全不一样
The crime scenes are completely different.
也许凶手在清理现场之前
Maybe the killer was interrupted before he could
- 被打断了 - 验尸官怎么说
- clean this one up. - What does the coroner say?
无名氏的报告还没有出
Still waiting for the report on John Doe,
但是西蒙凯利已被认定是谋杀
but Simon Kelly's been ruled a homicide.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
我联系了一个我认识的医生
I made contact with a doctor I know,
阿尔贝托桑切斯 他有个车载设备
Alberto Sanchez. He has a mobile unit
专为无家可归者派送
that dispenses long-acting antipsychotics
长效的抗精神病药物
to the homeless.
有什么情况记得告诉我
Let me know how that goes.
我们走
Let's go.
你怎么认识他的
How do you know this guy?
我和他一起做过一段时间的志愿者工作
I volunteered with him for a while,
确保没有人冻死或饿死
made sure no one was starving or freezing to death,
如果他们身体情况不佳就把他们带回医院
helped bring them in if they weren't doing too well.
你们对病人的了解有多少 我猜
How well did you get to know the patients? I'm guessing
给人打针不是什么交友的好办法
giving needles isn't the best way to make friends.
不光是药物治疗
Well, it wasn't just about the meds.
桑切斯 他还会发放食物和被褥并和他们聊天
Sanchez, he distributes food, blankets, conversation.
这些人面临最大的问题
You know, the biggest problem
其实是孤独
most of these folks have is loneliness.
你刚是说现场被清理过了吗
You said the scene was cleaned?
十分彻底
Thoroughly.
你知道有谁会做这种事吗
Do you know anyone who might do something like this?
每个人都觉得精神病患者是暴力罪犯
Everyone thinks the mentally ill are violent criminals.
相信我 他们更多时候是受害者
Believe me, they're far more often the victims.
- 说说西蒙吧 你治疗过他是吗 - 是的
- Tell me about Simon. You treated him? - Yeah.
西蒙是个不折不扣的好人
Simon was genuinely a good guy.
他只想痊愈
All he wanted was to be well.
他吃些什么药
What medication was he on?
氟哌啶醇 一种长效的安定药
Haloperidol long-acting.
能帮助治疗幻听
It helped with the voices.
但他三个月之前就不再来了
But he stopped coming in about 3 months ago.
为什么
Why?
他对副作用很反感
He was really frustrated with the side effects.
他说他不想
He said he wanted to get better
通过注射的方式来治疗 但是
without the injections, but...
不注射治不好
Only you don't without them.
是 至少对西蒙这样的来说是的
No. Not for someone like Simon.
他走后你没有找过他吗
You didn't keep track of him after he left?
我尽力了 探员先生
I do the best I can, Detective.
流浪汉都是来去无踪的
The homeless are transient by definition;
不会留下什么转寄地址
it's not like they leave a forwarding address.
这你怎么看
What do you make of this?
他打过架了
He was fighting.
- 和谁打的 - 有人花钱雇他打的
- Fighting who? - Whoever he was paid to.
那些小流氓 他们会来这儿
These young punks, they come down here
给我的病人们提供钱 毒品和酒
and they offer my patients money, drugs, alcohol.
然后让他们对打
And then they get them to fight each other
并拍下视频
while they make videos.
我报过警
I've called the police about this
但是没有任何回复
and nothing ever happens.
现在有回复了
Well, something's happening now.
你知道他们的名字或是相貌体征吗
You got names of these kids,descriptions?
我从没见过他们
I've never seen them.
我只知道他们年轻而且有钱
All I know is that they're young and they've got money.
- 使劲打 使劲打 - 流浪汉格斗
- Get him harder! Get him harder! - Bum fighting.
- 名字都这么恶心 - 这个山谷在几年前
- Even the name is disgusting. - There was a lot of talk
就有关于这种事的传闻
about this a few years ago in the valley.
我从来没有直接看到过
I never saw it firsthand.
现在这几乎是秘密活动
It's mostly underground these days,
但仍有人用这个赚钱 这是
but someone's still making money off it. This is
个高端华丽的网站 会员费可不便宜
a decently slick site. Membership's not cheap.
把他拉起来
Get him up!
- 那是他吗 - 是的 是西蒙凯利
- Is that him? - Yeah, that's Simon Kelly.
你认为做这个的人有可能杀了他吗
Do we think whoever made this could have killed him?
他们会从拍打斗片
Would they go from making fight films
进而去拍凶杀片吗
to making snuff films?
我觉得不像正常进程
Doesn't feel like a natural progression.
好吧 我们来查清楚 你能追踪这网站吗
Well, let's find out. Can you trace the website?
能 他们是些傻瓜 他们提供了贝宝账户
Yeah, they're idiots. They have a PayPal account.
我给网络犯罪部门打电话
I'll call E-Crimes.
让他们追踪那些钱
Follow the money.
对 找到那些做这垃圾的寄生虫
Yeah. Find the parasites who are doing this crap.
我不喜欢这些家伙
I don't like these guys.
你认识这个人吗
Do you recognize this man?
真恶心
That's gross.
他是谁
Who is he?
西蒙凯利
Simon Kelly.
他两天前在山谷里被杀了
He was murdered 2 days ago in the valley.
两天前
Two days ago
我在慕斯科卡参加高尔夫慈善锦标赛
I was at a charity golf tournament in Muskoka.
如果你不信
If you don't believe me,
你可以给司法部长打电话
you can call the attorney general.
他和某个法官
He and some judge,
跟我与家父搞了个四人对抗赛
they made up a foursome with me and my dad.
你看 我们还有证据证明你网站上的
You know, we also have proof that the PayPal account
贝宝账户是你的同伙
on your website was set up
伊恩辛克莱建立的
by your associate, Ian Sinclair.
他在隔壁的房间里 和我同事谈话
He's in the next room, talking to one of my colleagues.
我的同伙 你把它说得那么不吉利
My associate? You make it sound so ominous.
伊恩是我最好的朋友
Ian's my best friend.
但这不代表我们什么事都一起干
Doesn't mean we do everything together.
就出卖你最好的朋友了 不错啊
Selling out your best friend? Nice.
你之前见过这个人吗
You ever see this man before?
没有 他是谁
Nope. Who is he?
目前是无名氏
John Doe for now.
他三天前被杀了
He was killed 3 days ago.
你那个时间段也有不在场证明吗
You got an alibi for that timeframe?
我们认为他的伤是你和你的同伙伊恩辛克莱
We think his injuries were a direct result of a fight
在山谷里组织的打斗的
that you and your associate Ian Sinclair arranged
直接结果 现在 我们可能只能证明你们共谋
in the valley. Now, we might only get you on conspiracy
犯了侵犯人身罪 但是相信我
to commit assault, but believe me,
等法官查出他的死因
when the judge finds out that it resulted in a death,
你会得到最重的刑 不得假释
you're getting maximum jail time, no parole.
不会的
No.
如果你有证据的话 你会逮捕我的
If you had anything on me, you'd arrest me.
所以如果我是在密谋策划或者随便什么
And so what if I was conspiring or whatever?
谁在乎呢
Who cares?
他连个名字都没有
He doesn't even have a name.
你有没有想过也许这些流浪汉 我也不知道
Do you think that maybe these hobos, I don't know,
想要喝醉 找点乐子呢
might wanna get drunk, have some fun?
我是说 如果有人给他们点钱
I mean, so what if someone gives 'em a couple of bucks
还让他们感觉自己像电影明星呢
and makes 'em feel like movie stars?
哦 所以你才这么做 为了
Oh, so that's why you do it? To fulfill
- 满足他们做明星的梦想 - 不
- their dreams of stardom? - No,
不是的 好吧 我什么都没做
no! OK, I'm not doing anything!
你们这些警察可真不现实
You cops are unreal!
你们保护那些垃圾 然后你们来骚扰
You protect garbage like that, and then you harass
像我这样的纳税公民
tax-paying citizens like me.
喔 你这会儿成纳税人了
Oh, you're a taxpayer now.
那么 告诉我吧 等我们检查你的银行账户
So, tell me, when we check your bank accounts
找到你售卖非法音像制品的收入证据时
and find evidence of income from illegal video sales,
我们还会发现你曾经申报过吗
are we also going to find out that you declared it?
或者我应该在逐渐增多的起诉里
Or should I add tax evasion to the list of charges
加一条逃税吗 麦肯齐先生
that are mounting against you, Mr. MacKenzie?
什么
What?
他在西蒙凯利案件中的不在场证明查证了
His alibi checks out for the Simon Kelly murder.
反正我就从没想过要把他扯到那件案子上去
I never liked him for that one anyway.
我想让他承认那起无名氏案
I want to get him on the John Doe.
你做不到了 这个刚刚送来了
You won't. This just came in.
法医判定他是自然死亡
The coroner ruled it death from natural causes.
这不可能啊
That can't be right.
晚期肝硬化导致的肝衰竭
Liver failure due to advanced cirrhosis.
结束了 艾登 法医已经裁定了
It's done, Aidan. The coroner has ruled.
得放他走
Gotta let him go.
我能帮你吗
Can I give you a hand with that?
好吧
OK.
我的双手
My hands,
它们不是很灵活
they don't work so good.
是 呃 关节炎
It's the, uh, arthritis.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
鹰嘴豆
Chickpeas.
试试看 它们对你有好处
Try 'em. They're good for you.
西蒙 兄弟 他总是给我些像这样的东西
Simon, man, he was always giving me stuff like this.
西蒙还给过你什么
What else did Simon give you?
他给我各种各样的东西
He gave me all kinds of stuff.
因为他在准备他的重大旅行 哈
'Cause he was going on his big trip, eh?
对啊 他给了我这个
Yeah, he gave me, uh, this.
棒球棒
Baseball bat.
用来保护我自己
To protect myself.
我不...我不用它 我只是带着它
I don't... I don't use it; I just carry it around.
- 你说西蒙要去旅行吗 - 哦 是的
- You say Simon was going on a trip? - Oh, yeah.
去北方
Up north.
住在野外
Live in the wild.
远离一切
Get away from everything.
对了 他还给我钱
Yeah, he gave me money too.
- 他给你钱 - 是的
- He gave you money? - Yeah.
- 他从哪得到的钱 - 打架
- Where'd he get the money? - Fighting.
还有他妈妈
And his mom.
他妈妈 爱丽丝吗
His mom? Alice?
爱丽丝 是的
Alice, yeah.
她是个好厨师
She's a good cook.
当然 西蒙可不想让我告诉你这个
Of course, Simon wouldn't want me to tell you that.
他不喜欢她来这儿
He didn't like her coming around,
he didn't like her coming around.
爱丽丝两天前的晚上在这儿吗
Was Alice here 2 nights ago,
- 当西蒙... - 我不知道 我不知道
- when Simon was... - I don't know, I don't know.
我们能不能不...
Can we not...
我们能不说那事儿吗
can we not talk about that?
鹰嘴豆怎么样
How are those chickpeas?
还行
They're OK.
给你
Here you go.
我为你朋友感到遗憾
I'm sorry about your friend.
是啊 我也是
Yeah. Me too.
凯利夫人
Mrs. Kelly.
不好意思 现在真的不合适
I'm sorry, now is not a good time.
凯利夫人 我知道你一直和你儿子有联系
Mrs. Kelly, I know you've been in contact with your son.
我很多年都没见过西蒙了
I haven't seen Simon in years.
我们能就谈一下吗
Can we just talk?
我儿子已经死了 还有什么好谈的
My son is dead. What good will talking do?
好吧 我在努力找出是谁杀了他
Well I'm trying to find out who killed him.
你能不能就帮我一个忙 看一眼这张照片
Can you do me one favour and take a look at this picture?
你认得这个盘子吗
Do you recognize that dish?
对不起 我帮不了你
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
指纹与现场
Fingerprints are a match
打碎的盘子上的相吻合
for the broken dish at the scene.
爱丽丝凯利谎称
Alice Kelly is lying
她和儿子没有任何联系 为什么呢
about having any contact with her son. Why?
她不想让家里其他人知道
She didn't want the rest of her family to know.
因为...
Because...?
因为她丈夫和女儿明白西蒙病的有多严重
Her husband and daughter understood how ill Simon was.
但爱丽丝仍然希望他能好起来
But Alice was still hoping that he'd get better
然后回家来
and then he could come home.
母亲通常是最后一个
The mother is often the last one
放弃患精神分裂症孩子的人
to give up on a child with schizophrenia.
罗伯特和曼迪想知道西蒙是怎么死的
Robert and Maddie wanted to know how Simon died.
爱丽丝看起来一点也不好奇 这正常吗
Alice doesn't seem the least bit curious. Is that normal?
没什么是正常的
There is no normal.
但当我们一开始告诉他们的时候
But when we first told them,
她直接就进入了防御模式 仿佛她已经知道了
she went straight into defensive mode, as if she knew.
但却不想知道 典型的创伤后应激障碍症状
But didn't want to know classic PTSD symptoms.
我不知道你有没有听说
I don't know if you've heard,
我就某些话题差不多算个自学者
I'm a bit of an autodidact on the subject.
- 自学者 - 白昼俱乐部里的词
- Autodidact? - Word of the Day Club.
是我新学的 意思是自学的
It's my new thing. It means self-taught.
好吧 那么
OK, so,
关于西蒙的谋杀 爱丽丝有可能知道些什么
it's possible Alice knows something about Simon's murder
但她无法应付心理创伤
but is too traumatized to deal with it.
也许她知道凶手是谁
Maybe she knows who the murderer is
她在保护他
and is trying to protect him.
或者她可能在保护她自己
Or maybe she's trying to protect herself.
她杀了她自己的孩子
She killed her own kid?
他给她造成了很多痛苦
He caused her a lot of pain.
他不是故意的 但...
He didn't mean to, but...
这会发生 我见过
it happens. I've seen it.
好吧 所以
OK, so,
她努力想要照顾他 而他跑开了
she's trying to take care of him, he runs away.
她想保持联系 他不让她这么做
She wants to stay connected, he won't let her.
然后他告诉她他断了药
Then he tells her he's going off his meds
准备北上 居住在大陆之外的地方
and heading up north and gonna live off the land.
或许她生气了
Maybe she got angry.
或许她认为是在帮他
Or maybe she thought she was doing him a favour.
或许她只是失去了理智
Or maybe she just lost her mind.
好吧 不管发生了什么
Well, whatever happened,
爱丽丝凯利是新的头号嫌犯
Alice Kelly is our new prime suspect.
搜查队带回了一个园林工
Uniforms brought in a parks worker.
他发现什么了吗
He find something?
是的 漂白剂
Yeah. Bleach.
那是他妈妈吗
Is that the mother?
是的
Yeah.
总有一天我会讨厌这该死的工作
Some days I hate this damn job.
会花很长时间吗
This gonna take long?
我会尽快的 请坐
I'll make it as quick as I can. Have a seat.
你发现了一些空的漂白剂瓶子
So, you found some empty containers of bleach.
对 介意告诉我为何因此把我带到市区来吗
Yeah. Mind telling me why that gets me brought downtown?
这周有个无家可归的人在山谷被杀了
A homeless man was murdered in the valley this week.
有人用漂白剂清理了犯罪现场
Someone cleaned up the crime scene with bleach.
你发现了什么
What did you find?
一公升的瓶子 大概有五六个
Onelitre bottles, like 5 or 6 of 'em.
这么说 这些流浪汉是自相残杀 还是怎样
So, uh, these bums killing each other off, or what?
你在垃圾里发现其他东西了吗 比如衣物
Did you find anything else in the garbage? Clothes?
我真的没注意
I didn't really pay any attention.
我只是 警察问我有没有发现些异常的东西
I just... Cop asked me if I saw anything unusual.
我想不通 比如...
I figured, like...
谁会在该死的峡谷里
you know, who needs bleach
用漂白剂呢
in the middle of a friggin' ravine?
你还记得牌子吗
Do you remember the brand?
是成批生产的 跟我们工作用的那种差不多
Institutional stuff. Similar to what we use on the job.
但不是一种吗
But not identical?
不是 我们用的是蓝瓶的 而这些是白瓶的
No. We have blue bottles. These were white.
好吧 我想让你
OK. I'm going to have to ask you
看些图片
to look at some pictures.
是漂白剂的吗
Of bleach?
瞧 这是所选的清洁剂
Voila. Our cleaning agent of choice.
布莱特克斯工业质量漂白剂
Blytex Industrial Quality Bleach Agent.
- 那个园林工确定吗 -他说他确定
- The parks worker is sure? - Says he is.
布莱特克斯漂白剂是怎么回事
Blytex. What's with the bleach?
在距离现场大约四分之一英里的地方
Some empty containers were
发现了一些空瓶子
found about a quarter-mile from the scene.
那是他们在医院用的牌子
That's the same brand that they use at the hospital.
什么
What?
爱丽丝凯利最近回去工作了
Alice Kelly recently went back to work
做西南总部的管理员
as an administrator at Southwest General.
那里离山谷不到两英里 她有办法
Less than 2 miles from the valley. She has means,
有动机 看看他们有没有少漂白剂
she has motive. See if they're missing any bleach.
- 如果少了的话 - 那就申请搜查证
- And if they are? - File for a warrant.
你从厨房拿了所有刀具以后
Once you get all the knives from the kitchen,
就去检查一下池边小屋
check the pool house.
这太荒谬了 好了 在我和我的律师谈话之前
This is ridiculous. All right, I want you all to leave
- 我希望你们都离开 - 你就是律师
- until I speak to my lawyer. - You're a lawyer,
凯利先生 你知道搜查证的作用
Mr. Kelly. You know how a search warrant works.
- 你有这个的钥匙吗 - 我们知道
- Have you got a key for this? - We know
这对你来说有多难
how difficult this is for you.
你们 仅仅因为我妻子
Do you, eh? Just because my wife was
和我儿子有联系并不能说明她就是罪犯
in contact with my son does not make her a criminal.
凯利先生 警方必须要调查
The police have to investigate, Mr. Kelly.
调查毛线 她是一位伟大的母亲
Investigate what? Mary Mother of God,
你认为会是她杀的吗
do you think she killed him?
她是这世上
She's the only person in the world
唯一没有放弃他的人
who didn't give up on him.
你们这群人是怎么了 都瞎眼了吗
What's wrong with you people Are you blind?!
警探 我发现了些东西
Detective? I might have something here.
这个纽扣的背面有血
There's blood on the back of this button.
你把大部分血迹洗掉了 但留下了
So, you washed most of the blood out, but left
足以让我们检测的痕迹
just enough for us to test.
我们会在这件衬衣上
Are we going to find your son's DNA
发现你儿子的DNA吗 凯利夫人
on this shirt, Mrs. Kelly?
你不能这么对我妻子说话
You do not speak to my wife like that.
凯利先生 你不能干涉
Mr. Kelly, you can't interfere.
请你就待在这
Stay right here, please.
爱丽丝 请你过来
Alice, please come over here Alice.
- 先生 请退后 - 爱丽丝 到这边来
- Sir, back up, please. - Alice, come here.
先生
Sir.
那些你不能拿 那是我儿子的
You can't take those. Those belong to my son.
很抱歉 你刚刚证实了
I'm sorry. You just confirmed
这是被害人的财产
this is property belonging to the victim.
它们是私人财产
They're private.
夫人 夫人 别紧张 你需要坐下
Ma'am, ma'am, relax. You need to go sit down.
- 它们归私人所有 - 夫人 你需要坐下
- They're private! - You need to sit down, ma'am!
- 不 - 立刻
- No! - Now!
听着 别碰她 把书给我
Listen, you leave her alone. Give me the books.
先生 后退
Back up, sir!
- 我明白了 - 不 你不明白
- I got it. - No you don't.
罗伯特
Robert!
我的肩膀 啊
My shoulder. Ah!
它错位了
It's dislocated.
我不是有意伤害他的
I didn't mean to injure him,
但他一直挣扎...
but he just kept struggling...
他袭警了
He assaulted a police officer.
西蒙被谋杀了 大家都认为
Simon was murdered, and everyone thinks
你跟这事有关
you had something to do with it
因为在这件事情上你
because you have been lying
一直都在对大家说谎
to everyone this entire time!
妈妈 你到底什么时候才承认
When are you gonna admit it, Mom?
他已经走了
He's gone!
他已经走了好几年了
He's been gone for years.
呃 凯利先生 我想跟你道歉
Um, Mr. Kelly, I wanted to apologize to you.
对于之前发生的事 我真是感觉糟透了
I feel really terrible about what happened earlier.
你们已经足够长时间地剥夺了我的权利
You've denied me my rights long enough.
我要打电话
I want my call.
或许你会愿意接受他的道歉
You might want to accept his apology.
是他撤消了对你的指控
He's the one who got your charges dropped.
我想是我该道歉才对
I guess I'm the one who should apologize.
我不是有意伤害你的
I didn't mean to hurt you.
你当然不是有意的 如果你跟我一起的话
You didn't. If you'll come with me,
我会送你回家的
I'll take you home.
如果你愿意的话我可以送他回去
I can do that if you want.
我顺路 凯利先生 我们走吧
It's on my way. Mr. Kelly?
爱丽丝 爱丽丝 你在家吗 非常感谢
Alice? Alice, are you home? Thanks very much.
别动
Don't move.
外面到处都是搜查小队
Units are out everywhere.
- 没有她的踪迹 - 我们证实了凶器
- No sign of her. - We confirmed the weapon.
上面满是西蒙的血迹
It has Simon's blood
和爱丽丝的指纹
and Alice Kelly's fingerprints all over it.
她把它放在了显眼的位置 这几乎相当于供认
She left it in plain view. It's as good as a confession.
那么为什么我不开心呢
So why am I not happy?
因为她没有供认 她逃走了
Because she didn't confess; she ran.
实际上 她供认了但同时逃走了
Actually, she confessed and she ran at the same time.
那是否跟因为杀了自己的孩子
Is that consistent with feeling guilty
而感到愧疚相符呢
over killing your own child?
老实说 我不知道那跟什么相符
Frankly, I don't know what it's consistent with.
她的行为说不太通
Her behaviour doesn't make a lot of sense.
罪犯很愚蠢 而悲痛让人更愚蠢
Criminals are stupid. Grief makes you stupider.
她杀了自己的儿子 有什么能说得通这一点呢
She killed her own son. What makes sense about that?
不 医生是对的 我是说 首先她回避我们
No, the doc is right. I mean, first she stonewalls us,
然后她自套绞索
then she puts the noose around her own neck?
她到底想做什么呢
What's she trying to do?
听说我们锁定嫌犯了
I hear we have a suspect.
- 你们找到她了吗 - 没有
- You find her yet? - No.
搜查小队正在找 他们会找到的
Units are looking. They'll find her.
等找到她以后 她将面临二级谋杀罪指控
When they do, she's facing second degree.
杀人案告一段落 干得漂亮
Homicide is signing off. Nice work.
我认为不是她干的
I don't think she did it.
哦 艾登 别这样对我
Oh, Aidan. Don't do this to me.
你总是这么对我 你想多了
You always do this to me. You're overthinking it.
- 这讲不通 - 什么讲不通
- It doesn't add up. - What doesn't?
- 指纹还是刀子 - 这位母亲
- The prints, or the knife? - The mother.
是的 她摸过凶器
OK, she handled the weapon.
但这并不意味着就是她杀的
Doesn't mean she killed him.
我觉得他说得对
I think he's right.
她的行为并不意味着有罪
Her behaviour doesn't indicate guilt.
她的做法似乎是在否认
She's acting like she's in denial.
我们不知道全部内情
We don't have the whole story.
这个交给律师处理吧 我们只需要逮捕案犯
Leave it to the lawyers. We just pick 'em up
并移交 你的预感不都是对的
and hand 'em over. Your hunches aren't always right.
但也并不总是错的
They're not always wrong either.
请便吧 我们会标记成已经结案
All yours. We're marking it solved.
嘿
Hey,
我得走了 有些家里的事要处理
I gotta go. Some family thing.
嗯 我会回来的 半个小时
Um, I'll be back. Half an hour.
抱歉 我耽搁了
Sorry, I got held up.
这个给你
If you want.
谢谢
Thanks.
事情怎么样了
So, what's happening?
我们在外面又增加了二十辆巡逻车
Well, we've got 20 extra patrol cars out there,
但至今还是一无所获
but so far nothing.
你这半个小时发生了什么
What happened to half an hour?
我姐姐觉得她中风了
My sister thought she was having a stroke.
虚惊一场
False alarm.
- 那是什么 - 更年期
- What was it? - Menopause.
她有点多疑 她是家里的长女
She's a bit of a hypochondriac. She's the oldest,
而我是最小的女儿 相差六岁
I'm the youngest. Six.
这么说你姐姐是位忧郁症患者
So, your sister's a hypochondriac
而你是位医生 你一直利用这一点
and you're a doctor. You ever take advantage of that,
被她搞得有点焦头烂额了吗
mess around with her a bit?
如果我是那种人的话 我可能会的
I might, if I were that kind of person.
哦 我觉得你是那种人
Oh, I think you're that kind of person.
你对我的了解还不足以做出判断
You don't know me well enough to judge.
我错了吗
Am I wrong?
你近乎痴迷了 或许更甚
You're borderline obsessive. Maybe more
也许比"近乎"更严重
Maybe more than borderline.
你对你姐姐也是这么说的吗
Is that what you say to your sister?
除非她让我这么做
Only if she asks for it.
你在日记中发现什么了吗
You find anything in the journals?
是
Yeah.
他经历了很多痛苦
It's a lot of suffering.
可怜的孩子被幻听折磨
This poor kid was tormented by voices,
尤其是最近三个月
especially the last 3 months.
- 自从他停止服药 - 是
- Since he went off his meds. - Right.
"它们对我耳语 但声音很大
"They whisper at me, but loud.
昨晚又将我吵醒"
They woke me up again last night."
接着
And then...
"它们藏在暗处 但我知道它们在那儿
"They hide, but I know they're there.
我想让它们走开 但当它们不在时
I want them to go away, but when they do,
我很孤单 然后我又怕它们回来"
I'm lonely, and then I'm afraid they'll come back."
我不禁在想
You know, I can't stop thinking...
什么
What?
也许西蒙不是被谋杀的 也许他是自杀
Maybe Simon wasn't murdered; Maybe he killed himself.
所有的证据都指向这一点
I mean, everything points to it.
他最后的几篇日记
These last few journal entries
读起来像一篇长长的遗言
read like one long suicide note.
只是最后一篇日记
The only problem is
和我的猜想相悖
my theory falls apart with the last entry.
他很快乐
He's happy.
怎么讲
Happy how?
他说 "我想通了
He says, "I figured it out.
都会好起来的"
Everything is gonna be better."
我看看
Let me see.
这是自杀愉悦症
It's called suicide euphoria.
他很快乐因为能不再遭受折磨
He's happy because he's not tormented anymore.
他做出了决定
He's made a decision.
西蒙凯利是自杀的
Simon Kelly committed suicide.
我很确定
I'm pretty sure of it.
那为什么爱丽丝凯利
Then why is Alice Kelly
表现得像个谋杀嫌疑犯
behaving like a murder suspect?
她感到愧疚 不能挽救他
She feels guilty; she couldn't save him.
但证据却显示另有隐情
The evidence tells a different story.
也许不是
Maybe it doesn't.
多久能见到法医
How soon can we meet with the coroner?
刀锋的锯齿边缘
The knife's serrated edge
与喉部伤口吻合
is consistent with the throat cut.
小伤口是被害人抵抗时
The smaller cuts are defensive wounds incurred
招致的自卫伤口
while the victim struggled.
那不是自卫伤口
The small cuts aren't defensive wounds;
是犹豫伤
They're hesitation wounds.
一个自杀者抹脖子会犹豫吗
A suicide who slashes his own throat?
我从未见过
I've never seen it.
我见过 七年前的梅布伦特里案
I have. Maybrintly case, 7 years ago.
看看这个横向切口
Take a look at the transverse throat cut.
拜托 这是被害人自己造成的
Please. It's self-inflicted.
就算是自己造成的
If it was self-inflicted,
他为何放弃使用惯用手 所以不可能
he would have had to use his weaker hand. Not likely.
西蒙是左撇子
Simon was left-handed.
我不知情 你确定吗
I don't have that. Are you sure?
是的 这是他的照片
Pretty sure, yeah. This is him.
棒球手套戴在右手
Glove's on the right hand.
西蒙的日记显示
Simon's journals indicate that
他的自杀意图始于
his suicidal ideation began
大约三个月前
approximately 3 months ago,
当他停用安定药时
when he stopped taking antipsychotics.
他表现为临床抑郁症 精神病症状加重
He's clinically depressed, increasingly psychotic.
这是他的最后一篇日记
This one is from his final entry.
他在和折磨自己的声音对话
He's talking to the voices that tormented him:
"今晚我要开始一场旅行
"I am going on a big trip tonight,
不会再回来
and I'm not coming back.
这次 你不会跟来了"
And this time, you can't come with me."
这是自杀 莉莉
It was suicide, Lily.
是 那晚我要检查四具尸体
Yeah, I had 4 bodies that night,
家属前来认尸
families coming in to identify,
等着死因报告
waiting for the cause of death.
我会处理好的
I'll make it right.
曼迪 有你母亲的消息吗
Maddie. Have you heard from your mother?
- 我们上楼去 - 不 我没事
- Come on, we'll go upstairs. - No it's OK.
是我妈妈杀了西蒙吗
Did my Mom kill Simon?
不
We don't think so.
他 他是自杀的 对吗
He... he killed himself, didn't he?
你为什么来 曼迪
Why are you here, Maddie?
是... 是我妈妈
It's... it's my mom.
我担心她会伤害自己
I'm afraid she's gonna hurt herself.
你知道她在哪儿吗
Do you know where she is?
是的
I think so.
她在这儿 谢谢 我来处理
All right, she's here? Thanks, I got it.
爱丽丝
Alice.
我们搞清了西蒙的事
We know about Simon.
他做了什么 你做了什么
What he did, what you did.
很抱歉我们拿了他的日记
I'm sorry we had to take his journals,
但我不后悔读了它
but I'm not sorry that I read 'em.
我感到自己多了解了他一点
I felt like I got to know him a little bit.
真实的西蒙
The real Simon, you know?
为他的北上旅行做准备
Getting ready for his big trip up north,
试图独立起来
trying to be independent.
他不知道自己有多严重
He didn't know how bad he was getting.
但你知道
But you knew.
我无法想象看着他旧疾复发
And I can't imagine how hard it must have been
有多艰难
watching his illness come back.
那天晚上你找到他
And then that night when you found him...
有好多血
There was so much blood.
起初我以为是别人干的
At first I thought it was someone else.
我不能把他扔在那儿
I couldn't leave him like that.
我给他穿上他最爱的衬衫
I put on his favourite shirt.
让他看起来很好
To make him look nice, you know?
很干净
Clean.
我擦掉了所有的血迹
I made everything clean.
我不想让罗伯特和曼迪知道
I didn't want Robert and Maddie
西蒙是自杀的
to know that Simon had killed himself.
他们会自责
They would have felt so bad.
这不是他们的错 是我的错
It wasn't their fault; It was my fault.
爱丽丝 听我说 这不是你的错
Alice, listen to me. It wasn't your fault.
你也无能为力
There's nothing you could have done.
为了救西蒙
I let everything fall apart
我的生活都完了 为了什么
to save Simon. And for what?
我明白你的感受
I know how you're feeling.
你觉得悲痛永远不会消失
All right? You don't think it's ever gonna go away,
你知道自己像个胆小鬼 但你不在乎
and you know you're being a coward, but you don't care,
因为你只想结束这痛苦
because you just want this pain to stop.
你想结束一切 闭上眼睛
You want everything to stop so you can close your eyes
一了百了
and feel some peace.
相信我 爱丽丝
Trust me, Alice,
事情会变得…
things are going to be... Ah...
我抓住你了 抓住你了
I got you, I got you, I got you, I got you.
没事
I got you.
我抓住你了
I got you, I got you.
从这种悲伤解脱出来
Is a week long enough to recover
一周的时间够不够
from this kind of depression?
不够
Mm, no.
但我想她不会自杀了
But I don't think she's suicidal anymore.
我不知道该说什么 当我想…
I don't know what to say. When I think...
- 你会没事的 爱丽丝 - 妈妈
- You're going to be OK, Alice. - Mom?
在车里 我…
In the car, I had the...
我和我妻子第一次真正交流
the first real conversation I've had with my wife
在... 天呐 这么多年来
in... God, years.
多沟通
Have more.
他们不会有事吧
You think they're gonna be OK?
人们的恢复力总是很让我惊叹
It always amazes me what people can recover from.
他们为何不能
Why not them?
又有任务了 你还要来吗
Looks like we're on. You still want in on this?
错过什么也不能错过这个
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
使劲点 抓住他
Harder than that! Come on, get him.
使劲
Harder shots.
- 够了 - 嘿 伙计
- That's it. - Hey, dude.
- 终极对决 - 快来看
- Domination. - Come join the party.
揍他
- Oof! - Get him.
揍他 使劲 我来拿相机
Get him, come on! Hit! I'll take that camera.
- 去你的 快跑 - 拿下他们
- Screw you, dude. Go. - Take 'em!
趴下
Stay down.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 格兰特麦肯齐 - 还有伊恩辛克莱
- Grant MacKenzie... - And Ian Sinclair.
你们因共谋袭击罪被捕
You're under arrest for conspiracy to commit assault,
- 还有教唆罪 - 以及妨碍司法公正
- aiding and abetting. - Obstruction of justice.
公共饮酒 行为不端
Open air drinking, disorderly conduct.
- 乱丢垃圾 - 决斗罪
- Littering. - And duelling.
- 决斗也算 - 决斗罪
- Duelling?! - Duelling?
写在法条里了 一人向另一人
It's still on the books. It's a crime to provoke a person
发起决斗的挑战视为犯罪
to challenge another person to fight a duel.
太棒了
Awesome.
时不时抓几个小毛贼
Feels good to take down some plain old criminals
感觉不错
once in a while.
团伙抢劫银行很罕见
Hardly a bunch of bank robbers.
抓他们也一样
They'll do.
# 你说这世界不公平 #
Well, you say that it's not a just world